{
    "id": "267573f45c1d490daf225f8d52a8c332",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You will not succeed …………………………. you work really hard.",
            "description": "Unless means if not. ",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "in case"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have worked in this office ………………………… twenty years.",
            "description": "Use for with duration.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She accused me ……………………………… poisoning her cat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "about",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He left ten minutes …………………………..",
            "description": "Ago is used to count back from the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "ago"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. you follow your doctor’s advice, you will get well soon.",
            "description": "If expresses a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Martha along with her friends ……………………………. arrived.",
            "description": "When two nouns are connected with and, the verb agrees with the former. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What …………………………. you do then?",
            "description": "The word then shows distance in time. Hence, a past tense is used here. ",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "do",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy has been missing …………………….. Monday.",
            "description": "Use since with the starting point.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It ………………………. a hot day, I didn’t go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "being",
                "was",
                "been"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "One of the hens ……………………………… missing.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after one of.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither John nor his wife ………………………… there.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after neither/nor.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is collecting money for …………………………..",
            "description": "The homeless means all homeless people.",
            "answers": [
                "homeless",
                "the homeless",
                "homeless people"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}